

Aafaq Ahmad

Sr. Content Moderator and Team Lead

- Ghouri town phase 5-A, street 3-C, house # 722, 44000 Islamabac

Profile

I am an energetic, ambitious person who has developed a mature and responsible approach to any task that I undertake. Accustomed to working in team- oriented, fast- paced environments. As a graduate with two year experience in management and almost two year experience as content moderator in leading Social Media company BIGO Technologies I feel myself fit for the this vacant post. In my previous role, I improved the performance and of my team by 35%. I overall and consecutively maintained A+ KPI throughout the year. I know languages include Urdu, English, Punjabi, Saraike and can moderate content efficiently containing these languages.

Employment

Sr. Content Moderator & Team Lead

Jun 2020 - Present

Bigo Live Technologies, Islamabad

- Content Authentication
- Content Filter
- Management of illegal content according to company rules (Videos/Live Streams/images)
- Team Management
- Maintained A+ KPI

Sales Manager & Team Lead

Feb 2020 - Jun 2020

Codex BPO, Rawalpindi

- Maintain good working relations with various network departments to ensure the
- scheduling process flows smoothly.
- Monitor agent calls and provide feedback.
- Provide coverage in agent scheduling gaps.
- Ensure data and call quality.
- Adhered to company policies and scripts to consistently achieve call-time and quality standards.
- Sought out training opportunities to enhance customer relationship management abilities and further boost satisfaction scores.

Internships

Website Design and Development Internship

Feb 2019 - Jul 2019

Mega IT Solutions, Rawalpindi

• Learnt Html, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, PHP.

Personal details

Date of birth April 18th, 1998

LinkedIn

linkedin.com/in/aafaq-ahmad-494454136

Skills

MS Office

Social Media Management

Leadership

Programming

Project
Management/Management

Languages

English

Urdu

Punjabi

Saraiki

- Worked on the PHP framework Code Igniter.
- Made stunning and fully responsive website designs.
- Oversaw back-end development using PHP to maintain website integrity, security and efficiency.
- Made web based management systems and CRUDs.

Data Management Internship

Aug 2019 - Oct 2019

PTCL (Pakistan Telecommunications Limited), Islamabad

- Data Management
- Interpret Data according to company rules and policies
- Data Auditory

Certificates

Website Design and Development

Feb 2018

- Learnt Html, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, PHP.
- Worked on the PHP framework Code Igniter.
- Made stunning and fully responsive website designs.
- Oversaw back-end development using PHP to maintain website integrity, security and efficiency.
- Made web based management systems and CRUDs.

Education

Matriculation (Science)

Mar 2014 - Apr 2016

The Pak Educational Public Scgool, Multan

A Grade

Intermediate (Pre-Engg)

Apr 2015 - May 2016

Rise College of Science, Multan

A Grade

BS (Computer Science)

Oct 2016 - Aug 2020

PMAS Arid Agriculture University, Rawalpindi 3.12/4.00 CGPA

Qualities

- Leadership
- Management
- Hardworking
- Punctuality
- Dedication

Hobbies

- Hiking
- Gym and Workout
- E-Gaming
- Meditation